Gerard P. Kuiper papers 1894-1992 (bulk 1949-1973)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series: IX: Publication Files. This series is arranged alphabetically. It is a record of Dr. Kuiper’s writing career. This subgroup is divided into 6 series: Solar System. Stars and Stellar Systems, articles, lectures, papers. Atlases. Book Chapters. Notes, 1944-1974.
  - Subseries 5: Book Chapters, 1944-1965
    - Sub-subseries 2: By title of chapter - publication title unknown.
      - Spectra of the planets v.4, 1947-1950 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 6: Notes, 1926-1973
    - Notes taken by Kuiper of lectures by other scientist, 1926-1929; 1946-1948 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Yerkes course notes, 1937-1939; 1949 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Science notes, 1937-1942 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Celestial mechanics course notes - Yerkes, 1948-1954 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - New projects, 1947-1950 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - The Solar system course, 1950-1951 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Planets and satellites loose notes, [1960] (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Spectroscopy course, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Astronomy courses, [1961-1964] (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - High dispersion stars, [1963] (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Planetary sciences notes, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Planetary sciences course notes, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Series X: Research, 1894-1973:
  The series is arranged alphabetically. Research files are divided into six series: Asteroid Program (1949-1954), Proposals with Dr. Kuiper’s involvement (1946-1972), Subject files (1894-1973), Hawaii (1957-1970), Chilean Project 1959-1963, Site Surveys 1964-1973.
  - Subseries 1: Asteroid Program, 1949-1954
    - Kuiper’s notes, 1950-1951 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Survey computation, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Finished records - series b-r, t-x, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Malinin’s measures, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Fujita’s measures, undated (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Kent, J.T. measures, August 1950; September –December, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - CA Cook asteroids, August 1950 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - CA program miscellaneous, [1956] (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Survey computations – Prints of papers I and II, 1949-1953 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Asteroid records Cincinnati Observatory - Stephenson's measures, 1950-1955 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - B-series, no comet, August 1950 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - C-series, no comet, September 1950 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - C-D series, no comet, October 1950 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - E series, no comet, November 1950 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - F series, no comet, December 1950 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - F-G series, no comet, December 1950-January 1951 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - G-H series, no comet, February 1951 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - H-I series, I 62 comet, February - March 1951 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - I-J series, I 62 comet, I 43 comet, I 53 comet, March-April 1951 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - K series, 917 comet, April-May 1951 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - L series comet 917, May-June 1951 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - M series comet 917, June-July 1951 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - N series, no comet, July-August 1951 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - O series, no comet, August-September 1951 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - P series, no comet, September-October 1951 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Q series, no comet, October-November 1951 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - R series, no comet, November-December 1951 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - R-S series, no comet, December 1951- January 1952 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - T series, no comet, January - February 1952 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - U series, no comet, February 1952 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - V series, no comet, March 1952 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - W series, no comet, April 1952 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - X series, no comet, May 1952 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - UT Asteroid 14, cloudy night, January 4,1954 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - UT Asteroid 10, 9 - wrong object, January 1,1954 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - UT Asteroid 9, January 3, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - UT Asteroid 40, Asteroid 9, January 9, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - UT 40 clouds, 3 o.k., January 10, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - UT 44, January 7, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - UT Asteroid 44, asteroid, January 11, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - UT Asteroid 14. Looked for 44 but couldn't find. Looked for Pluto but not available, December 30, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - UT Asteroid 10, December 31, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - UT 2, June 30, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - General, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Cook telescope, August – December, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Cook telescope, January – June 9, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Cook telescope, May 27 – June 9, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Cook telescope, June 26 – July 6, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Cook telescope, January 21- May 26, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Observing record of Asteroid Program with 10 inch Cook telescope, 1950- 1952 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Minor planet charts (asteroid charts?) B-G series, 1950-1951 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Asteroids to be found B-F series, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Final report rediscovery and observation of lost asteroids, 1952-1954 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 2: Proposals by year - Kuiper involvement, 1946-1972
    - Infra-red project proposed for Navy task order, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - For the support of the astronomy by the National Science Foundation, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Collaboration University of Arizona, University of Indiana and Ohio State University, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Proposal for a Coude stellar spectrograph and telescope for the southern hemisphere, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Assistance in the operating budget of the Infrared and Microwave facility of the McDonald Observatory, 1958; 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - The Development of the McDonald Observatory, University of Texas, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Assistance in preparation of the Lunar Atlas Photographs, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Specifications for the McDonald Observatory 60 inch telescope, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - A Ground-based program of lunar studies, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Statistical studies of faint asteroids supplementary application, December 1960 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - 28 ft. Infrared telescope, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Construction of the 60 inch optical telescope, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Infrared spectroscopy applied to planets and stars, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Institute type support of programs at the Lunar and Planetary Laboratory, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Partial support of a 60 inch Lunar and planetary telescope, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Proposal for 1961 summer institute of atmospheric physics (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Superior Seeing proposal, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Biophysics problems in planetary probing, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Laboratory research on gases occurring in planetary atmospheres, 1962-1964 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Principal investigator program for Ranger block III, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Research and development of low voltage, high resolution electron microscopes with special applications to biological materials, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Evaluation of the Ranger VII data, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - Investigation of photogrammetic compilation of Ranger television imagery, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 48)
    - 5 year program in selenodesy and lunar cartography, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 49)
    - Astrometric and astrophysical investigations of comets, minor planets and satellites, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 50)
    - Large camera with wide angle all reflecting optics for astronomical application, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 51)
    - Wide angle reflecting telescope research, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 52)
    - Multi-color basic photometry for planets asteroids and stars brighter than 6.5, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 53)
    - Program of high altitude infrared spectroscopy of planets and stars II, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 54)
    - Program in selenodesy from photographic an laser observations, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 55)
    - Design and fabrication of 60 inch metal mirror telescope, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 56)
    - Completion of the wide angle reflecting UV camera, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 57)
    - Study of early history of the moon and solar system, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 58)
    - Higher resolution molecular spectroscopy with application in astrophysics, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 59)
    - High resolution Fourier spectrometer for infrared planetary spectroscopy, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 60)
    - 70 inch Telescope, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 61)
    - High resolution infrared Fourier spectroscopy of planets and stars, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 62)
    - Infrared spectroscopy of the planet from 1-5.6 u with the medium resolution LPL Fourier interferometer from NASA airborne IR observatory, [1971] (Box 41, Folder 63)
    - Infrared spectroscopy of the Galilean satellites at the Jupiter opposition in 1972 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Interpretation of Mars topography, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Photometric monitoring of infrared stars and variable M super giants in visual and infrared spectral regions, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - A Program of infrared fourier transform spectroscopy for astronomy, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Study of seasonal and secular variations on Mars, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 10 ft. infrared telescope at the Lunar and Planetary Laboratory of the University of Arizona, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Contracts and grants for which Dr. G.P. Kuiper is designated as principal investigator or director, 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Reporting information for various agencies, 1960-1972 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: United States Air Force (USAF)
    - Air Force Correspondence and progress reports, 1960-1970 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Chilean Observatory, 1958-1960 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Handbook of the Solar System, 1953-1960 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Research directed toward a photo-telescopic selenodetic measuring program, 1967-1970 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Lumicon Project, 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Lunar and planetary studies, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Lunar Investigations, 1963-1965 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Lunar laser, 1965-1971 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Old lunar project contract, 1958-1960 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - 1.5 Meter light gatherer, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Photographic lunar atlas, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Photography image content, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Planetary properties research, 1958-1960 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Research directed toward a lunar physiographic study, 1965-1968 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Selenodetic measuring program, 1967-1970 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Solar system research, 1956-1960 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - 12 inch Telescope, undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 4: Central Intelligence Agency (CIA)
    - Russian Astronomical Literature - Final Report, [1950’s- 1960’s] (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Russian Astronomical Literature (2), 1958-1960 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Subseries 5: Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL)
    - Ranger program, 1963- 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Surveyor, 1967-1969 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Mercury Venus Mission, 1969-1973 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 6: National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA)
    - General, 1963-1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Construction of a 60 inch lunar and planetary telescope, 1963-1970 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Electron microscope, 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Infrared spectroscopy stars and planets, 1961-1963 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Investigation of the lunar surface, 1967-1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Lunar studies research, 1959-1961 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Planetary and satellite spectroscopy, 1969-1974 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Planetary spectroscopy and surface studies, 1962-1972 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Polarimetry of Venus, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Solar system studies with 16 inch telescope, 1964-1966 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 7: National Science Foundation (NFS)
    - Asteroids, [1952-1955] (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Astrometric investigations, 1963-1967 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Development of two Interferometer telescopes, 1959-1961 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Infrared microwave telescope, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Lunar atlas investigations, 1955-1960 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Solar system studies, 1957-1959 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Stars and stellar systems, 1952-1961 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Stars and stellar systems, 1962-1974 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Summer institute of dynamical astronomy, 1964-1966 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 8: Office of Naval Research
    - General, 1961-1967 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Aid in preparing an encyclopedia of the Solar System, 1951-1953 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Aid in preparing an encyclopedia of the Solar System, 1954-1961 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Infrared observations of planetary spectra, 1954-1961 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Infrared planetary studies by multi-channel recordings, 1961-1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Planetary gases, 1960-1968 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Solar radiation, 1950-1952 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Statistical studies of the asteroids, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Studies of the origin of the Solar System, 1949-1954 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 9: Subjects Files, 1894-1973
    - Sub-subseries 1: Air Pollution
      - Research in Southern Arizona air pollution. Grant proposal to the Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1968-1970 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - The Air pollution problem in the Southwest United States. Proposal to NASA, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Pima County air pollution control advisory council regulations revisions, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Observational photographs of air pollution in the Tucson Basin, October 1968-November 1969 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Observational photographs of air pollution in the Tucson Basin, July 20, 1968-September 30, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Air Pollution notes by Dr. Kuiper, [1967-1971] (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Rules and regulations Pima County Air Pollution Control District, [1967-1970] (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Pima County Air Pollution Advisory Council, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Pima County Air Pollution Advisory Council, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Pima County Air Pollution Advisory Council, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Pima County Air Pollution Advisory Council, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Pima County Air Pollution Advisory Council, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Pima County Air Pollution Advisory Council, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Air Pollution photographs, undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Douglas Smelter, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Air Pollution photography Book 1 and 2, index, [1967] (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - 1968-1969, Air Pollution Photography; 3 boxes (Box 45)
      - 21 - slide containers, October 15, 1967- April 15, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - 26 - slide containers, April 17, 1968-August 6, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - 37 - slide containers, August 7, 1968- November 4, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Air Pollution Photography, 1969; 3 boxes (Box 46)
      - 36 - slide containers, November 5, 1968-April 3, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - 37 - slide containers, April 8, 1969-September 12, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - 9 - slide containers, September 16, 1969 - November 6, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Sub-subseries 2: General
      - Absorption tube, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Astronomical telegrams, 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - B stars, [1947] (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Balloon flights - Page/Glen Canyon Polar-scope, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Binary Double(BD)stars, [1950-1952] (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Celestial navigation method, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Charts of proper motion star fields, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Chilean observation project, 1959-1963 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Comet Bennett, 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Comet Kohoutek, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Comet notes, 1966-1973 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Dispersion tables for spectrograph, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Double star statistics, 1937-1938 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Double stars, [1950-1953] (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Double stars reduction sheets and graphs, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Duplicity of cluster stars, undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Dwarf stars, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Dwarf stars radial velocity program, [1943] (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Earth albedo, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Earth atmosphere - interior, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Earth - Infrared transmissions, [1947] (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Earth mountain formation, convection currents, 1952-1953 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Earth upper air H2O, 1949-1950 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - Gerard P. Kuiper Airborne Observatory, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Ground based and balloon borne lunar planetary observation, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Harvard summer school, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - High altitude flights Mars and Venus - balloon, 1953-1958 (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - High altitude sites and Infrared astronomy, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 28)
      - Imaging of Mercury, 1970-1972 (Box 47, Folder 29)
      - Infrared equipment, 1947-1952 (Box 47, Folder 30)
      - Infrared equipment Galactic scanner, 1946-1947; 1956 (Box 47, Folder 31)
      - Infrared imagery, 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 32)
      - Infrared projects - general, 1943-1947 (Box 47, Folder 33)
      - Infrared projects, grating spectrometer, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 34)
      - Infrared spectrometer, [1944-1949] (Box 47, Folder 35)
      - Instrument design, [1953-1956] (Box 47, Folder 36)
      - Jupiter catalogue - incomplete, 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 37)
      - Jupiter material/observations, 1965-1968 (Box 47, Folder 38)
      - Jupiter radio noise and red spot, undated (Box 47, Folder 39)
      - Jupiter's satellites, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 40)
      - Lab comparison spectra, undated (Box 47, Folder 41)
      - Lab reflection of metals, undated (Box 47, Folder 42)
      - Lunar comparison lava flows in New Mexico, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 43)
      - Lunar comparison studies with west Texas crater, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 44)
      - Lunar comparison with lava fields in New Mexico and Mexico, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 45)
      - Lunar comparison lava flows - Oregon, 1966-1969 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Mars, George Ellery Hale on -, 1894; 1909; 1934 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Mars, 1949-1950; 1963-1965, (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Meteor impacts, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Micrometer measures of stars, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Monograph of stars, [1943] (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Mount Agassiz telescope, Flagstaff, 1970-1973 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Mount Hopkins Observatory Site - Smithsonian, 1965-1970 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Mount Hopkins multiple mirror telescope, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Mount Hopkins multiple mirror telescope, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Orbiting Astronomical Observatory, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Community College proposal and report, 1969-1971 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Planetary drawings originals and reproductions, 1909-1958 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Planetary notes, [1950-1956] (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Planetary research bibliography, [1950] (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Planets spectra, [1940’s- 1950’s] (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Pluto, 1950-1956 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Rocket flare triangulation test, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Rocket flare triangulation test, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Ross stars, [1940’s] (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Satellite discovers, 1949-1950 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Saturn, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Secondary Science Training Program, 1966-1968 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Smithsonian Tables revisions, [1950] (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Space Race with Soviet Union, 1957 - 1959 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Soviet Union news release on Venus and Mars probes, 1957-1972 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Spectrometer balloon, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Spectrometer balloon, 1963-1965 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Spectrometer electronics, 1963-1965 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Star Survey 36 inch telescope, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Unidentified flying objects, 1951-1956; 1961 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Uranus, naming of the satellites of Uranus, 1948-1949 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Venus, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Venus notes by Kuiper, [1950-1955] (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Water vapor band, [1964] (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Water vapor measurements for Space Science Building, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 10: Hawaii - Observation Sites, 1957-1970
    - Haleakala site survey, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Haleakala site survey, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Mauna Kea correspondence and newspaper clippings, [1960s] (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Mauna Kea Observation Station dedication, July 20, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Mauna Kea site survey, 1963-1964 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Mauna Kea site history by Alika K. Herring, June 15, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Mauna Kea water vapor readings, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Mauna Loa site survey, 1957-1963 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Notes by Kuiper, [1960’s] (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Observatories of the University of Hawaii, [1960s] (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, [1960s] (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Telescope proposals, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Report on site surveys, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Volcanic eruptions observations, 1960; 1967-1970 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Weekly weather reports, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 11: Chilean Project - Observation Sites, 1959-1963; 1957-1970
    - Chile Observatory meetings, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Chile trips, 1959-1962 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Chile, Santiago trip - photographs (1), undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Chile, Santiago trip - photographs (2), undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Chile Site Survey by Jürgen Stock nos. 1-13, 1960-1961 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Chile Site Survey by Jürgen Stock nos. 14-31, 1961-1963 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Chile Site Survey by Alika K. Herring, February 19,-March 6, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      (In the same notebook is Kuiper’s last Site Survey of Mexico. December 13-18, 1973)
  - Subseries 12: Other Site Surveys, 1964-1973
    - Baja California Cloud photographs, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Baja California confidential correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Baja California 60 inch B telescope, 1967-1972 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Baja California photographs, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Baja California Seeing Tests, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Baja California Site Survey Socorro Island, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Baja California Water Vapor, [1967] (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Catalina Site Survey by Alika Gerring, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Catalina Site Survey Seeing tests - Mount Bigelow, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Catalina Site Survey weather reports, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Cone Peak, California, undated (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Mexico - See also Box 59, folder 11, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Mount Lemon Catalina Infrared Site Test, 1971-1973 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Mount Logan, Canadian Yukon, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Mount Shasta, California, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Pikes Peak, Colorado, 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - San Francisco Peaks - Mt. Agassiz, [1963] (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Soldier Peak Site, [1969] (Box 51, Folder 2)